<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CognitiveTests</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="stroop_instruction">In the stroop test, a text spelling a name of a random color will be shown to you for a period of 3 seconds, 20 times. The color of the text will differ from the color that is spelled out by the text. After the text disappears from the screen, you have to press the microphone button and spell out the color of the text that was shown to you, NOT the name of the color spelled out by the text. Your goal is to correctly pronounce the name of the color of the text as many times as possible.</string>
    <string name="trail_making_instruction">In the trail making test, your goal is to connect the dots displayed on the canvas in the correct order, in 1 continuous stroke. In the first part of the test, the dots contain only numbers, you have to connect them in the increasing order. In the second part of the test, the dots have numbers and letters, you have to connect the dots and letters in the alternating manner, like this: 1A2B3C4D and so on. If you make a mistake, or remove your finger from the screen before connecting all the dots, the line drawn will be cleared and you will have to start again.</string>
    <string name="digit_substitution_instruction">In the digit substitution test, you will be presented with a series of symbols corresponding to digits. The legend depicting which symbol corresponds to which digit is visible at the top of the screen. During the duration of the test, that spans 2 minutes, you will be presented with a series of digits. You have to match the digit presented in the middle of the screen with the one of the symbols, to do that, press one of the buttons corresponding to the symbols, on the bottom of the screen. Your goal is to match as many symbols as possible during the time reserved for the test.</string>
</resources>